well I'm here to tell you that for as
long as 199 pesos and then all digital
processes
financial advisor you can get yourself
in insurance coverage yes
200 pesos
[Music]
online let me introduce you to Manulife
Philippines news products manualize 365
ready products
365 regular life which will secure your
family's future for as low as 249 pesos
Manulife 365 ready accident that will
cover you in case you get into an
accident for as low as 199 pesos and
manualize 365 ready Duo that has both
Life and Accident coverage that will
cover you up to 1 million pesos you just
need three requirements you must be in
good health you need a valid ID and a
debit request credit card for payment
you can check it out at
mangalife.com.ph by Dash Insurance Dash
online dot HTML my question